foreign
[Music]
Wildflower season is upon us and the
hillsides are swathed in white and gold
and blue
I had a day off from work so I took an
audiobook out to the meadow next to my
home and listened to fairy tales while
putting flowers in my hair and imagining
far-off kingdoms and castles
I got quite caught up in my Daydreams
and found that in no time at all it was
noon and time to get ready for a dinner
with my family that evening
I don't get to enjoy a lazy day too
often but it makes it that much more
special when it comes around
[Music]
I just had to take a moment to stop and
appreciate the wildflowers right now
it is so abundant and I feel like
this is the gift that we get for waiting
out the winter you know the winter was
so long this year and to get such
incredible beauty and abundance in
Return of that long cold weight is so
beautiful and I just couldn't be happier
right now
foreign
[Music]
I had as a young college student
I wanted to be a successful scholar and
spend days writing endless essays in the
dusty corner of a respected University
I ended up achieving a version of that
dream I got a scholarship and was
encouraged to enter a masters and PhD
program from a professor I greatly
admired I could see a future career in
my mind's eye
but something changed I realized the
academic pressure I was putting on
myself was masking a deep lack of
fulfillment I was pursuing this degree
simply because I was good at it never
stopping to ask myself if I actually
enjoyed it
[Music]
foreign
I concluded I'd simply gotten it wrong I
needed a new dream to work towards a
goal so my goal became being an editor
for a magazine and a Bookseller these
dreams seemed a lot more reasonable and
soon I was working for three different
magazines running a school publication
and later worked at a bookstore
full-time
even though I had once again achieved my
dreams I was still struggling to feel at
peace
[Music]
foreign
perhaps what I was missing was a good
relationship with more friends the
perfect place to live maybe I needed a
new dream altogether perhaps if I just
had everything lined up in life just so
things would be different
there was something much deeper that was
off something that was following me
everywhere it took a long time to admit
to myself that I was searching for peace
and achievements when instead I needed
to love and accept myself as a soul and
nothing else
my achievements could only be a
temporary Band-Aid over my wounds and
that was just it I was carrying my hurts
and pains and worries everywhere I went
and I had to heal those things first if
I was ever going to find a renewed zest
for life
so I moved to a small town started
working at a local school selling my art
at farmers markets and even started this
channel it wasn't my dream but I decided
that my new dream was to heal and to
find that sense of achievement Within
Myself no degrees relationships are
impressive resumes needed
simply trying to be kinder sitting with
myself growing a feeling that is
somewhere between fleeting joy and
sadness a sort of quiet peace and
contentment with who I am
I've now achieved a lot of dreams I
never thought I could I can now enjoy
them fully knowing that they aren't the
reason I'm happy I don't need to make
videos to make me happy I don't even
need to be able to run through a field
of wildflowers or spend evenings
painting to find peace and joy my legs
could stop working and my eyesight could
fail me and that's why there's something
much deeper that needs to guide me my
abilities are accomplishments don't make
up the core of what makes my light shine
and I hope the same for you that you can
find the source of Your Inner Light that
is not rooted in anything physical of
this world not even your physical self
something far deeper and perhaps harder
to understand but once you're open to it
absolute Magic
I find this light source and what
exactly it is to be a bit different for
everyone but you'll know it once you
find it like a kindred spirit coming
into your life familiar and true like
coming home after many years of looking
for happiness and things that are
impermanent and unpredictable
foreign
[Music]
on fixing some things in this room and
there is a ladder set up and my cat is
just dedicated to going up and down the
ladder again and again and again and
she's she's very noisy
mavi
[Music]
stop it my
it is so hard to film sometimes as you
can probably tell I've fallen in love
with this dress the version that is in
red I really really love as well you saw
me wearing it at the beginning of this
video I as I promised a couple videos
ago I wanted to find some more
sustainable clothing options to share
with you that are similar to the style I
often wear as I wear a lot of secondhand
you know clothing from Brands I wouldn't
normally support I did want to share
with you a brand I would actually
support and one that I hope to in the
future invest in several dresses to wear
for years and years to come the brand is
called Sunday floor I'm hoping I'm
saying that correctly but yes it's made
of a sustainable linen and it it's just
beautiful beautiful designs and I've
really enjoyed these two that I've been
wearing and so I will leave a link down
below to it if you are interested at all
the topic of this video you know is one
I've touched on before but I did want to
share how my dreams and my goals for the
future have changed so drastically over
the years you know and how I have
achieved a lot of goals I have and how
every time it has especially when I was
younger surprised me that the feeling of
gratification of achieving that goal was
so fleeting you know I I was not able to
create that lasting sense of being proud
of myself and who I am because I think I
was trying to connect that pride in who
I am to accomplishments
um and that just wasn't a sustainable
source for me in terms of appreciating
myself and valuing who I am
I really had to learn how to Value
myself as a human being you know without
any accomplishments by by just being who
I am and trying to be a little bit
better than I was the day before and and
that has had much more lasting impact
when you Embrace that journey of trying
to be a better person maybe connecting
with your spirituality or any form of
that that you know works for you it is
transformative because it makes you
realize that there is no such thing as a
truly ordinary life it doesn't matter
what you've accomplished or what you
look like or you know what your life
looks like to other people it's about
who you are and who you might be trying
to be and become and a big part of that
for me is connecting more to my spirit
and how I can connect with other people
through that awareness that we are all
here together and we're all
interconnected of course there were
things about my goals and situations in
the past that made it really hard to
find that sense of peace peace and
fulfillment I remember at one point I
was living in an apartment that was not
legally rented out to me and it was
infested with rats I had some roommates
that were fighting all the time and
screaming at each other and it was such
a difficult environment to find a sense
of peace and I definitely had to work
towards finding a way to move past that
phase of my life and find a new place to
live and of course it was much easier to
find that sense of fulfillment once I
was able to leave that situation because
it was affecting me so much but I know
that facing challenges in the future I
see now how important it is to stay
positive and hopeful you will develop
such an incredible strength that it
doesn't matter what life throws at you
you're going to be able to find a way to
get through it particularly when you're
not a hundred percent reliant on
external things to find that sense of
peace
sometimes it will be really hard to find
that source of light especially when you
are going through a really difficult
time but I like to think that's when
it's just as important and I know for
sure it is in those dark times that
we're often most ready to change and
develop who we are and to make big
decisions and even just within that
there's always something we can gain
from those difficult times at least that
has been my experience so far I have
memories that I've just wanted to erase
from my mind for so long getting to a
place where I can accept them and start
to try to see things that I gained from
working through experiences like that
and appreciating those and that all
those things make up who I am and I hope
you as well can go to this week feeling
a little deeper sense of appreciation
for who you are and how far you've come
I hope you share with me below your own
stories and your words of encouragement
to each other it is always so inspiring
I'm sending you much much love and I
will see you very soon goodbye
[Music]
foreign